Typhoon #13 is maintaining its gale force winds
as it continues to make its way north.
The storm struck South Daitou Island last night at roughly 11 p.m.
As of now, the effect on transportation in all areas...
Daikichi!
The TV says the bullet train is pooping!
Not pooping! Operating!
Pooping?
Operating!
They probably said, "The bullet train is operating on normal schedules."
That means it's running like as usual.
The bullet train is pooping!
Uh-oh. I gotta poop!
Jeez...
Typhoon #13 has changed its course and is gradually moving east,
where it's expected to make landfall in the Tokai area this evening.
She said there's a typhoon!
It's all right. Typhoons come every year...
Daikichi!
Outta toilet paper?
You should see how much I'm making!
Bring a ruler!
Boys are notoriously childish, but...
I feel your pain.
Bunny Drop
I dunno about tomorrow
It's different than a sacrifice Something's off
I don't think it's like some penalty game
So, why? I don't get it at all
I'm a little bit unsatisfied, but your presence
right now is more than just important
There's no such thing in this world
as something never-ending
Crying isn't painful, it's love's sweet drops, sweet drops!
I want to keep dreaming forever, ya know?
I want to be more kind, ya know?
As long as I'm with you, I'm happy
Girls sure are strong, ya know?
But sometimes we're weak, ya know?
Our wish is to be happy, happy, happy!
And those days will be happy, too!
Just wanna make you happy!
I'll pick you up early today.
Okay!
Kouki, let's go!
Awesome, right?!
We're gonna be late.
See ya later!
If you leave just enough space for the circles, then you'll write it like a pro.
Got it?
Teacher, how much is "just enough"?
Um...
How many centimeters? Millimeters?
How about we forget the circles?
Okay!
All right, the rest will be your homework.
For the next activity, all the first-graders are going to draw.
Meet up outside in front of your own morning glory.
Do you understand?
Yes!
Why are sandbags so heavy?!
It's still morning and I'm already beat...
And it had to be today that we've got tons to ship...
Thank you.
What's that?
My kids' educational insurance...
They're still in diapers!
If I waited 'til they got bigger, the insurance wouldn't mean a thing.
G-Good point.
We're enrolled too.
Although I kinda doubt he'll be college material with my genes...
We've got two, so it'll be pretty tight.
Ours is still a little squirt, so we got day-care fees too,
which is nothin' to sneeze at.
And he outgrows clothes faster than we can buy 'em.
Well, we're only contract employees, but it helps
that welfare and health insurance are included.
What about life insurance?
My wife took care of that for me.
The payout's pretty decent if I kick the bucket,
but she has universal life insurance.
The basic one...
You guys really are "fathers", aren't you?
I'm impressed.
There's nothin' to be impressed about.
I wonder how much insurance costs...
The brat next door is too damn noisy so we wanna move,
but the money just ain't there.
Yeah, I don't even know what I'm workin' for...
Take a good look at us!
Get married, and this is what happens!
I don't have a girlfriend, so there's no danger of that.
They're always bitchin' and moanin', yet...
Deep down, there's a sense of security...
I can't imagine them ever becoming like Rin's mother.
Kouki!
Sit down and draw!
Yikes!
Where's your drawing board?
Dunno. The ground's flat, so I don't need it.
That's not gonna work!
If I tell you to bring something, you bring it!
Get it right now! Run!
Wow, your drawing is really good, Rin!
Yeah, it is! It's great!
So pretty!
Really..?
That's really good!
The colors of these two flowers are slightly different.
Rin's drawing shows that with both bluish and purplish colors.
You have a sharp eye.
Kouki and those boys are wandering around again.
Kouki...
It's drawing time right now.
Kouki, your morning glories are looking splendid!
It would be a waste not to sketch them.
Do you like to draw, Kouki?
It's okay, I guess...
Mr. Tatsumi...
I'm in charge of this boy.
Why do you always, always bother everyone, Kouki?!
Sit down and draw!
And don't make any weird faces!
I got Kouki's hat!
Cut it out!
Hey! Kouki! Boys!
Stop fooling around!
Get back here!
I got it! I got it!
Rin?
Kouki!
Sit down and draw!
Don't let them get you in trouble!
'Kay.
That was incredible, Rin.
Kouki's always so weird, and he's scary when he gets mad.
He'll bully you, Rin!
No, he won't! I've known him since kindergarten!
Really?!
They're late...
You guys pick your kids up at 6 too, right?
Yeah. Cuttin' it close today.
Here they are!
All right! Let's get it over with!
Yeah!
Hello!
You got a little wet, huh?
Rin! Your father's here!
Hey...
I-I'm sorry...
Not at all. Don't worry about it.
I'll go get Rin.
The wind's really picked up, huh?
Yeah. I tried to get here earlier, but...
Am I the last?
Kouki's still here...
Daikichi!
There's a storm, huh?
Yeah. It's really coming down.
Sorry I'm late.
It's okay.
Look at that umbrella go!
Did something happen?
Uh-uh. I'm fine.
See ya!
Okay, later, Kouki!
Wanna walk home together?
Let's walk home together!
Sure!
I'm sorry, but you haven't been given permission so...
I know. But the wind is only gonna get stronger,
so let me try calling Ms. Nitani to see it's okay.
I'll have her talk to you too, to confirm.
Um... In that case...
We can go home early, too!
What's that?!
Well, we were just kidding.
Kouki!
Me too!
Rin!
That's dangerous!
Get behind me and follow along!
Hold it!
I'll bring you a towel.
The storm windows!
Cool! Lemme get this one!
Careful. Don't crush your fingers.
It's dark!
Y'know, it's kind of like a secret base!
It's in my eyes!
I'm gonna rinse it now, so don't open your eyes.
All right, dry the rest yourself.
Daikichi, your back is huge!
I know, right?!
Good evening! It's Nitani!
All right! Coming!
So you were able to get off work early...
I hope I didn't go too far.
Not at all! It was a big help.
Sorry. Kouki got soaked on the way here.
Really, I don't know where to begin to apologize...
That looks good on you!
Daikichi, let me borrow yours!
Again?! You mean "Mr. Daikichi", right?!
He said "Daikichi" is fine!
Yeah, I'm more comfortable with that.
That's right!
Just "Daikichi" is fine!
Rin, you're good at that!
I can use a knife, too!
You're already a young lady!
Daikichi does the fire, though.
I'll do it too!
But you never help out...
I'll cut too!
I'll lend you my knife!
Oh, no! Onions suck!
Don't touch it! Go wash your eyes out!
Where are you going?
Oh, no! I'm crying!
Y'know, we're making hamburger patties...
Yep... It looks delicious, doesn't it?
These are kind of strange...
They're not strange! Right?
Well, I'm sure they'll taste fine.
Rin! The eggs are boiled!
Can you peel them?
Okay!
Done!
Perfect!
Rin's eating it up...
Kouki, do you love your mom?
Sure. If only she didn't bug me...
There's a sense of security here too.
This one's mine!
Where are your manners?
Thanks for the food!
Kouki, use your chopsticks!
I know, I'm just getting it together.
It's good, isn't it?!
It is!
Food tastes better when we eat it together!
Let's eat here again tomorrow night!
Kouki!
That's good enough.
I'll finish up later.
Okay...
And then it hit him right in the head!
He's so excited...
He's never had this kind of fun before.
I'm so happy for this evening.
Thank you.
Oh, I didn't... I should thank you!
Teacher said we didn't need those circles!
Leaving work early was worth it.
Just to see that smiling face.
She's raising a child alone too...
Daikichi! Come here a second!
All right...
I think it's about time...
Should I call a taxi?
Oh, thank you.
Why don't you stay over?
Rin!
Well, Reina and her mom stayed over.
That was different!
See ya tomorrow...
See you!
Bye-bye!
Thank you, Rin.
Thank you very much.
We had fun, too.
Right?
Yep!
Bye-bye!
A sunny early Sunday afternoon
Let's go somewhere today
It's the same road I'm used to traveling
But I can see it sparkling so bright
With the sun shining down its warmth
And you here by my side...
I'm already high, high, high
I feel like dashing out
Sing, la, la, la
My voice out to forever
I'm already high, high, high
Ride the dancing wind
Sing, la, la, la
My voice springs up
The typhoon left, huh?
Looks like it.
Rin! Hey, Rin!
Kouki's here already!
He's early again!
Come on in!
You sure...?
Hold on!
Wait!
I wanted to open the storm windows...
Not a cloud in the sky!
See you later!
Kouki, we're gonna be late!
See ya later!